<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>announcement on Open Force Field Initiative</title>
    <link>//openforcefield.org/tags/announcement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in announcement on Open Force Field Initiative</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//openforcefield.org/tags/announcement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Third Open Force Field Consortium Workshop</title>
      <link>//openforcefield.org/news/may2020-meeting-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//openforcefield.org/news/may2020-meeting-announcement/</guid>
      <description>We are excited to announce the Third Open Force Field Consortium Workshop on May 4-5, 2020! This time we meet in Cambridge, MA and the venue has been generously provided by Pfizer, Inc. This workshop will be held just before the 2020 Workshop on Free Energy Methods in Drug Design, held on May 6-8, 2020 at the Novartis Institute of Biomedical Research, which is within a walking distance from Pfizer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aug 2019 Open Force Field Consortium Workshop</title>
      <link>//openforcefield.org/news/aug-2019-meeting-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//openforcefield.org/news/aug-2019-meeting-announcement/</guid>
      <description>We are hosting the Second Open Force Field Consortium Workshop in La Jolla, CA on August 30-31, 2019. The first two days of the workshop will focus on the progress update and future planning of OpenFF efforts in Year 2. The third day (Sep 1) is reserved for OpenFF team discussions, but open to interested Industry Partners. The event will be again hosted at UCSD campus, but please note that the venue has been relocated from Jacobs Medical Center used in January to the Skaggs School of Pharmacy and Pharmaceutical Sciences building.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>